

+447975671978

Trowbridge, Wiltshire, BA14 0LF

EDUCATION

PGCE Primary
 Bath Spa University
 Completed in 2021

Bachelor of Arts in English
 Southampton Solent University
 2:1, Completed in 2016

3 A-levels

Norton Hill Secondary School English Literature, Psychology and History Pre-University Completed in 2013

• 11 GCSEs

Norton Hill Secondary School
Completed in 2011

KEY SKILLS

- Copywriting / editing
- Communication
- Integrity
- Data analysis
- Creativity
- Adaptability
- Collaboration
- Problem-solving
- Time management

INTERESTS

- Crochet
- Literature
- Wine

REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST Full working history on request

Georgina Woodman

QTS Primary School Teacher

PROFILE

I am a dedicated, organized and methodical individual. I have good interpersonal skills, am an excellent team worker and am keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills. I am reliable and dependable and often seek new responsibilities within a wide range of employment areas. I have an active and dynamic approach to work and getting things done. I am determined and decisive. I identify and develop opportunities.

I have experience in customer service roles and am looking forward to the opportunity to continue to grow within this field of work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Forest & Sandridge Primary School | Class Teacher 2022 - Present

- Created lesson plans and resources to teach to a class of up to 31 students.
- Delivered high-quality learning and support to a variety of needs within the classroom.
- Communicated with colleagues and parents about class and individual progress and expectations.

Weston All Saints Primary School | Class Teacher 2021-2022

- Created lesson plans and resources to teach to a class of up to 90 students.
- Delivered high-quality learning and support to a variety of needs within the classroom.
- Communicated with colleagues and parents about class and individual progress and expectations.
- Supported with a variety of afterschool functions and creation of school-wide displays.

MC Publishing LTD | Production and Digital Assistant 2019-2020

- Managed social media accounts, and increased social media followings and clicks.
- Designed and built editorial pages and adverts using Adobe Photoshop, InDesign and Quark.
- Created original content, updated and mainted publication websites.

Circo Bar Bath | Assistant Manager / Social Media Manager 2016-2018

- Managed all social media accounts, creating fresh content and creation of ads.
- Organised a team of 10 to carry out the duties of the establishment.
- Designed Gin High Tea and Rum tasting events, delivering training to colleagues.

Crimson Publishing | Marketing Assistant Intern 2017

- Updated and creation of content for publication websites.
- Created a variety of new content for the publication's social media.
- Updating publications through Amazon Marketplace.
- Designed and published a variety of educational resources.

EVRI | Delivery Driver 2016

- Delivered a variety of parcels to the Bath area.
- Organised and sorted parcels for the Bath are